<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
<id>repoman</id>
<metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
<name>Sagora</name>
<name xml:lang="ca_ES.UTF-8@valencia">Sagora</name>
<name xml:lang="ca_ES@valencia">Sagora</name>
<name xml:lang="ca">Sagora</name>
<name xml:lang="es">Sagora</name>
<summary>Stream live music</summary>
<summary xml:lang="es">Emite música en directo</summary>
<summary xml:lang="ca_ES@valencia">Emiteix música en directe</summary>
<summary xml:lang="ca_ES.UTF-8@valencia">Emiteix música en directe</summary>
<summary xml:lang="ca">Emiteix música en directe</summary>
<description>
<p>SAGORA is free software, designed and developed by artists/researchers from the School of Arts of the National University of Quilmes, Argentina. It allows to connect multiple users in a virtual room and transmit audio in real time without canceling the signals, as usual in platforms commonly used for teleconferencing. This specific aspect makes it an extremely useful application for musical practice, in the cultural industry and education sectors, since it makes music rehearsals and/or concerts possible using the internet</p>
<p xml:lang="es">SAGORA es un software libre y gratuito, diseñado y desarrollado por artistas/investigadores de la Escuela Universitaria de Artes de la Universidad Nacional de Quilmes, Argentina. Permite conectar múltiples usuarios en una sala virtual y transmitir audio en tiempo real sin que se cancelen las señales, como sucede en las plataformas de uso común para teleconferencia. Esta particularidad lo transforma en una aplicación sumamente útil para la práctica musical, tanto en el sector de industrias culturales como en el de educación, ya que permite realizar ensayos y/o conciertos utilizando internet.</p>
</description>
<categories>
<category>KDE</category>
<category>QT</category>
<category>Audio</category>
<category>LliureX</category>

</categories>
<icon type="stock">sangora</icon>
<provides><binary>Sangora</binary></provides>
<keywords>
<keyword>stream</keyword>
<keyword>music</keyword>
<keyword>live</keyword>
<keyword>podcast</keyword>
<keyword>play</keyword>
</keywords>
<keywords xml:lang="ca_ES.UTF-8@valencia">
<keyword>emitir</keyword>
<keyword>musica</keyword>
</keywords>
<keywords xml:lang="ca_ES@valencia">
<keyword>emetre</keyword>
</keywords>
</component>
